footymad.net 2018-12-28

# Privacy and cookie policy - Footymad.net

Footymad Privacy Policy and info on cookie usage Cookies   
A "cookie" is an element of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Whenever you visit our website (unless you elect not to receive cookies), then your computer will store an identifying code in the cookie. We use cookies to help us (i) estimate and report our total audience size and traffic (ii) conduct research to improve our content and services (iii) to make your user experience more simple in a variety of different ways, for example you do not need to type in your user name each time you return to the site. At his or her option and at his or her sole expense and responsibility, any user may configure their browser to block or delete our cookies from his or her hard drive. However, by disabling cookies, certain site features and functionality may no longer work properly, or at all. Please note that we allow other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not our Privacy Policy. 

First-party cookies used   
'SessionID' - enables us to maintain the state of your login during your current browing session as you move across pages on our site(s). 'CaptchaID' - used in attempt to prevent automated software from performing actions during form submission, it expires upon successful captcha key entry. 'Google Analytics' - used to collect information about how visitors use Footymad's web sites, including the number of visitors, where they have come from and the pages they have visited. We use the information to compile reports, which help us to understand user behaviour on our site and how we might be able to improve our service. 

Examples of third-party cookies used   
'Facebook' - Facebook Social Plugin – embedding Facebook content.[ read Facebook's Privacy policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/)   
'Google+1' - Google+1 Social Plugin – embedding Google+1 content. [read Google's Privacy policy ](https://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/policies/privacy/)  
'Twitter' - Twitter Social Plugin – embedding Twitter content. [read Twitter's Privacy policy ](http://twitter.com/privacy)  
'Advertisement tracking (various)' - used to collect non-personal information about how visitors interact with advertising served on other websites before they arrive at Footymad and which advertisements our customers prefer. This information helps us deliver ads that are relevant to your interests, control the number of times you see a given ad, and measure the effectiveness of advertising campaigns. 

Privacy   
Your privacy is of the utmost importance to us. We gather certain types of information about our users, therefore we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. Please find below our privacy policy. 

We are Footymad and we own and operate this website ('Footymad.net', at footymad.net). Our registered address is Digital House, Threshelfords Business Park, Inworth Road, Feering, Colchester, CO5 9SE.  Please read the following policy to understand how we will deal with your personal data after it has been collected by us through your use of one of our platforms. Those platforms include our website, and any other channels as they evolve. 

Compliance with legislation   
We operate and are registered in accordance with all applicable data protection legislation in England and Wales. 

We may collect data about you, some of which could be personal, in a variety of ways, including:   
1\. when you register with the website;   
2\. when you purchase products or services from the site or from any of our other platforms;   
3\. when you enter competitions and/or complete surveys, and;   
4\. through the use of certain data capturing devices (for example studying which pages you read the most through the use of cookies). 

Use of personal data   
The information we collect may include, but is not limited to, details such as your name, your address, your e-mail address, your age, your gender, date of birth, phone number, and your credit or debit card details. 

We will not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes without your express consent. 

Unless we have your express consent we will only disclose personal data to (i) third parties if this is required for the purpose of completing your transaction with us (ii) other companies within our group, (iii) our professional advisers who are bound by confidentiality codes, and (iv) when we are legally obliged to disclose your data. 

By becoming a registered user you consent to receive from us by e-mail our newsletter and details of other special offers which we may think may be of interest to you. 

Third Party Advertising   
The ads appearing on this Website are delivered to you, on our behalf, by our web advertising partner. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or any other personal information), is used to serve ads. 

Links/Third Parties   
Please note that this privacy policy only addresses our activities from our servers. Other sites (including those our website links to and third party sites or services) may have their own privacy policies and practices, which we do not control. 

While we strive to protect your personal information, our network of sites contain links to partners, advertisers and third party Internet sites and services who may collect data in connection with sweepstakes, promotions, e-commerce, etc. They each have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of our policy and therefore we have no control over these independent policies or actions and are not responsible for their privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

Consent   
By disclosing your personal information to us using this website, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by us in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. 

Opt-Out Policy   
Registered users of the website who have elected to receive our newsletter always have the option to opt-out of receiving further information from us by clicking on the link at the end of each newsletter and via the website. 

Amendments to this Policy   
We may amend this policy from time to time however we assure you that we only use your data and for our legitimate business reasons and in order to give you a better user experience. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our homepage. 

Testimonials   
Some information and e-mails sent to us may be used as testimonials but no e-mail address or contact details will be displayed. 

Contacting Us   
If you have any questions or concerns about the information we hold about you, you can get in touch by filling in a short contact form, which can be reached by [clicking here](http://www.footymad.net/contact-us/index.shtml).
